jobsahead.com 2016-03-09

# JobsAhead : Privacy Policy

1\. Overview  
Monster Worldwide, Inc., Monster.com India Private Limited (a company owned by Monster Worldwide) and Monster Technologies, LLC, (each “Monster” or “Company”) are committed to respecting the privacy of our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to JobsAhead.com (sometimes referred to herein as the "Site" or “Web Site” ) and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion.

By registering or by using this site, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Statement. Please read this Statement carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities under law. If you do not accept the Privacy Statement stated herein or disagree with the way we collect and process personal information collected on the Web site, please do not use it.

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in the United States and India. The information we gather on JobsAhead.com may be shared within the Monster-affiliated companies on a worldwide basis in order to deliver the products and services we offer to employers such as searches for job seekers or in order to undertake analysis of our database such as aggregate profiling of our registered users. "Affiliated companies" means entities that control, are controlled by or are under common control with Monster Worldwide, Inc.

JobsAhead.com may contain links to other Web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from our Site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.  
We also do not control the data use practices of either (a) employers or others who may access your information on this site, or (b) third party ad networks and other third parties with whom we work to serve you personalized ads on our sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and opt-out choices of those third parties so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

2\. Collection and Use of Information by JobsAhead

**Information We Collect and Retain**  
You do not have to give us any personal information in order to perform job searches or to read the content portions of our Site. We collect the following general types of information about you when you visit our Sites: personal information, demographic information, behavioral information, and indirect information. Sometimes we collect combinations of all these types of information. In each case, it is indicated on the web site whether any personal or demographic data must be provided to use the requested service or not.

_Personal information_ is information that can be used to identify you, or any other individual to whom the information may relate, personally. We do not collect personal information unless you choose to provide it to us. Some examples of personal information that we collect in some areas of our Site, depending on the services you use and local law, are: 

  * Your name 
  * Address 
  * Email address 
  * Telephone number 
  * Contact information 
  * Billing information 
  * Information about third parties, such as references or contacts, that you provide to us if you have their express written consent to do so 

_Demographic information_ is information that is not unique to you in the sense that it refers to selected population characteristics, such as your ZIP code or postal code, age, preferences, gender, race or ethnicity, occupation, career history, interests and favorites.

We also collect _behavioral information_ regarding how you use our site and mobile applications, the areas of our site that you visit, what services you access, and information about your computer hardware and software including your IP address, geolocation, browser and operating system type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is necessary for analyzing the use of resources, troubleshooting problems, preventing fraud, and improving our services.

In addition,  JobsAhead may collect _indirect information_ about you when you use certain third party services on our web site and the collection of such information is considered necessary for that purpose.

We do not collect sensitive personal data or information of users like password of your e mail account; password of your JobsAhead account (as it automatically get saved in the  JobsAheadserver  when you create an account or register with JobsAhead and not authorized by  JobsAhead for access unless desired under any legal obligation); financial information such as Bank Account details or Credit Card or Debit Card or other payment related details; physical and mental or other health conditions or medical records and history; Biometric information such as finger prints, voice & facial patterns and DNA any other sensitive information which is confidential or sensitive by its nature.

We may personalize the advertising that you are shown on our sites or other sites with which we have a business relationship. In order to provide this personalization, in addition to information we collect about you on our sites, we acquire information (including personal, demographic, behavioral and indirect information) about you from third parties who provide it to us.

In some areas of JobsAhead.com, we request or may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible. In other areas, we collect or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your PIN code, age, preferences, gender, interests and favorites. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. Examples of areas on the Site where we collect personal or combined personal and demographic data are pages where you can open a My JobsAhead account, sign up to use a service, post a resume, enter a contest or purchase a product. In addition, we may indirectly collect information about you when you use certain third party services available on JobsAhead. For example, if you register on JobsAhead by using your Microsoft Passport user name and password, you authorize us to have access to and store the information in your Passport account profile; such information will be subject to, and treated in accordance with, the policies and practices described in this Privacy Statement.

We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of JobsAhead.com, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by us. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses, but is not linked to your personal information.

We may sometimes afford you the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioral, preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. If you do provide such information, you are thereby consenting to the use of that information in accordance with the policies and practices described in this Privacy Statement. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving e-mail or other communications about particular products or services.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about JobsAhead.com or other Monster Sites or refer a job posting to a friend, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site(s) or view the job posting. We do not store this information.

3\. Our Use of Your Information  
We use the information we gather on JobsAhead.com, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the Site, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer.

If you have provided consent for us to do so, we may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from us or our affiliated companies or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered.  
We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the Site, and if you have requested, information on new opportunities and additional job postings which may be of interest to you. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you.

In addition, at the time of registration for a My JobsAhead account, you have the option to elect or not elect to receive additional communications, information and promotions, including without limitation, free informational newsletters from us relating to topics that may be of special interest to you, such as career management advice. 

We have areas on the Site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback you submit in these areas becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or to contact you for further information.  
  
**Users’ Consent to JobsAhead to Use the Information**

By registering with JobsAhead.com, by managing your profile, or opting in when presented with choices, you have explicitly consented for us to use your information, subject to local law, in the following ways: 

  * to allow you to create an account; 
  * to create a profile for you based on information that you have provided to us; 
  * to contact you about Site updates, informational and service-related communications, including important security updates; 
  * to provide you additional communications, information, and promotions such as newsletters and career advice; 
  * to inform you of other products or services available from Monster or its affiliates (“Affiliates” means entities that control, are controlled by or are under common control with Monster Worldwide, Inc.); 
  * to enable you to provide feedback, to contact us and for us to respond to you; 
  * to conduct surveys, questionnaires, promotions and contests, and to provide the results thereof such as success stories and contest winners; 
  * to provide information about you and your potential interest in job postings to employer customers; 
  * to provide products and services to employer customers to complete the recruitment and hiring process, such as accessing the searchable resume database; 
  * to provide products and services that enable users to network, post information on bulletin boards, view and compare profiles, and career background and experience; 
  * to generate internal reports about the use of our site; and 
  * to provide ‘forward to a friend’ features. 

Some of our products and services, such as our searchable resume database and networking, enable third parties to see your personal information and to contact you. Profile information may be used for networking with other community members or may be visible to employers who are using the Sites. In addition, portions of your searchable resume (but not your contact information) may be made public in your networking profile.

**Information you post in public areas of the site or place in the searchable resume database will be accessed, used, and stored by others around the world, including those in countries that might not have legislation that guarantees adequate protection of personal information as defined by your country of residence.** By providing your personal information for inclusion in our database, you acknowledge that you consent to your information being used as described here. While Monster takes measures to safeguard your information from unauthorized access or inappropriate use by third parties, Monster does not control these third parties and we are not responsible for their use of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of the JobsAhead Sites. Accordingly, you should ensure that you do not post sensitive information, including personality profiles, to any JobsAhead Site.

4\. Choices Regarding the Disclosure of Personal Information to Others   
We do not disclose your personal information to third parties, or your combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of JobsAhead (such as the areas you visit or the services you access), except as set forth below. 

  * We disclose information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if you indicate that you would like to receive information about the opportunities, products or services of third parties at the time you register for a My JobsAhead account, we supply your contact information to third parties such as employers, recruiters, data aggregators, marketers or others for the purpose of sending you e-mail or otherwise communicating with you. We use data we have about you (such as the interests and preferences you have expressed) to determine whether you might be interested in the opportunities, products or services of a particular third-party. 
  * We disclose information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. 
  * We disclose information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 
  * We disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. You will be notified of sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party via email or through a prominent notice posted on the JobsAhead Sites. 

5\. Other Uses of Information  
We also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to JobsAhead (for example, the number of visitors to JobsAhead's job search area) with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Site and other Monster Sites and how those visitors use the said Sites.

We supply technology, hosting and related services to other leading companies to power recruitment areas on their Web sites (sometimes referred to as "Hosted Career Sites"). Personal and/or demographic information supplied by you in Hosted Career Sites becomes part of the Monster database, but it is not accessible by anyone other than you, Monster and the company concerned without your consent.

Information gathered on a page in a Hosted Career Site or on a co-branded page (such as that of a contest co-sponsored by JobsAhead and another company), may become the property of the other company or of both us and the other company. In that instance, the use of such information by the other company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company. We are not responsible for that company's use of your personal or demographic information.

If you apply for a position on JobsAhead or through a Hosted Career Site, you may be asked to provide information on your gender, race or other protected status where permitted by applicable law. Some employers are required by law to gather this information from job applicants for reporting and record-keeping requirements. You should understand that if provided, this information will be used by employers only in accordance with applicable law and will not be used in making any negative employment decisions. All information provided will be kept separate from your expression of interest in any job opportunity. Providing this information is strictly voluntary and you will not be subject to any adverse action or treatment if you choose not to provide this information.

6\. Personal Information on Resumes and Profiles  

Since JobsAhead is a career site, we give you three options regarding the accessibility of your resume: 

  1. You can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers. Not allowing your resume to be searchable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product.  

  2. If you allow your resume to be searchable without making it confidential and hiding your contact information, then all parties with access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) will have access to your resume.
  3. If you have a confidential resume, but apply to a job posting on JobsAhead, the employer to whom you send your resume will be able to view your contact information. 

We attempt to limit access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) only to paying employers, recruiters, hiring managers, and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not gain access to this database. We are not responsible for the use made of resumes by third parties who access such resumes while they are in our searchable database. You may remove your resume on JobsAhead at anytime, but, employers, recruiters and others who have paid for access to the JobsAhead resume database or to obtain a copy of that database as well as parties who have otherwise gained access may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes or profiles in these instances.  
****

7\. Posting to Public Areas of JobsAhead   
Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of JobsAhead such as in online forums or chat rooms, or in the JobsAhead searchable resume database, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of JobsAhead.

8\. Use of Cookies  
We use "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize  JobsAhead pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to JobsAhead, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing.

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on JobsAhead.

9\. Use of Web Beacons  
JobsAhead Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. 

You may not decline web beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.

10\. Access to and Modification of Your Information  
You may review, correct, update or change your My JobsAhead account information at any time.

To change My JobsAhead account information, simply log into your My JobsAhead account, go to your Account Profile, review your account information and, if you wish, edit it with the options provided. [Click here](http://www.jobsahead.com/my/login.html) to access your My JobsAhead Account Profile page.

If you opted to receive newsletters, commercial e-mails or other communications from JobsAhead or third parties at the time you created a My JobsAhead account, but subsequently changed your mind, you may opt-out by editing My JobsAhead Account Profile as described above. If you previously opted not to receive such communications, you may later opt-in by editing My JobsAhead Account Profile as well.

We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use of JobsAhead more efficient, practical, and relevant. Of course, you can delete your resume from JobsAhead's online database, close My JobsAhead account at any time in which event we will remove all our copies of your resume from JobsAhead, My JobsAhead account information except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the Internet. 

11\. Security of the Personal Information  
We have implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.  
  
**Important Information**

_**Security**_   
You are responsible for ensuring that your log-in credentials (your username and password) are kept confidential.

Monster has implemented technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. Notwithstanding such measures, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. Moreover, one of our primary purposes is to provide you with a platform to broadcast the information in your resume and profile widely in order to maximize your career opportunities. Such an environment does present a risk that unauthorized third parties will view this data, so you should refer to our Security Center for additional information on conducting a safe job search. Further, your resume should not contain any sensitive data that you would not want made public. You should be aware that resumes may be monitored by your current employer.

We also use cookies, web beacons, and Java Script to administer our site and deliver a personalized experience. For additional detailed information on each of these, please see below.

12\. Children  
JobsAhead and the other Monster Sites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

13\. Safe Harbor  
We participate in the Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Framework arising out of the U.S. implementation of the European Union Data Protection Directive. We have certified adherence to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles for each of the Monster Sites. For more information about the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles and to view our certification, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/) Web site. If you would like to contact us directly about the Safe Harbor program, please send an e-mail to safeharbor@monster.com.

14\. Changes to Privacy Statement  
If we decide to materially change our Privacy Statement for JobsAhead, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.   
If at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Statement, please feel free to email us at [PrivacyPolicy@Monsterindia.com](mailto:PrivacyPolicy@Monsterindia.com) or call us at 040-66116000 and speak to one of our representatives. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly answer your question or resolve your problem.

15\. Contact Information  
If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Statement, please feel free to  contact us online at [PrivacyPolicy@Monsterindia.com  
](mailto:PrivacyPolicy@Monsterindia.com)  
or at :

| By post / mail :  | L D Pandey, Legal Department,  
Monster.com India Private Limited  
Tapasya Building, 6th Floor,   
Plot No. 5 EFGH, Sector-126.  
Noida, 201301, U.P., India   
---|---  
By telephone:  | 0120-4024100   
  
We will use reasonable efforts to answer promptly your question or resolve your problem. 

**Use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and Java Script**

_Cookies:_  JobsAhead uses "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends.   
A cookie is a text file that is either stored in your computer’s memory temporarily (a “session” cookie) or placed on your hard drive (a “persistent” cookie) by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

When you return to the  JobsAhead site, cookies enable us to retrieve the information you previously provided, so you can easily use the features that you customized. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. For example, if you personalize  JobsAhead pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences).

We predominately use “session” cookies, which are not permanently stored on your hard drive. Session cookies expire after two hours of inactivity or when you close your browser. When you carry out a job search or apply online a large amount of data is processed by our system and transferred through each page of the search or application process. This information includes your job search criteria, data that identifies your resume, covering letter, the job you are applying for, your right to work in the relevant country and the results of any questionnaire you have completed as part of the online application process as well as demographic information that is not unique to you. “Session” cookies allow us to keep track of this data until you have completed your search or application. We also use cookies to identify users who have been banned from using our forums for behavior that contradicts our terms of use and to track click streams, for load balancing and to enable you to navigate through the site using redirection pages.

We use “persistent” cookies primarily to ensure that we do not show you pages that you have already seen and to personalize your site experience and save you time. “Persistent” Cookies enable us to recognize whether you have responded to any poll or seen an advertisement or information notice placed on the site so that we do not show you the poll, advertisement or notice again the next time you visit our site. If you are a recruiter and have an alliance arrangement in place with  JobsAhead we also use “persistent” cookies to recall your alliance status and display your correct pricing information when you access our site. The “persistent” cookies we use will remain on your computer after you have left our site and will expire when you log out of the Site or 60 days after your last visit for security cookies, 90 days after your last visit for poll response and alliance cookies, or two years after your last visit for advertisement and information notice cookies.

We also allow other companies to display advertisements to you while you are visiting our Sites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements from the other companies’ servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. Monster has no control over, and is not responsible for, the practices of those third party advertisers. Monster encourages you to review the policies of such advertisers.

You will find additional information about the following third party ad servers at [www.doubleclick.com](http://www.doubleclick.com/); [www.atlassolutions.com/privacy](http://www.atlassolutions.com/privacy); and [www.omniture.com/en/privacy](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy). We use other third party ad servers as well; a way to opt out of third party cookies is to modify your browser settings to decline cookies as described at the end of this statement. You may also [click here](http://inside.monster.com/ad-network/inside2.aspx) to see a list of many of the companies that Monster works with in connection with serving personalized ads. Otherwise, if you do not wish to allow your session visitation information on our Sites to be aggregated and analyzed by Omniture, or used by Omniture to tailor dynamic content to your specific interests, you may utilize the following opt out mechanism [www.omniture.com/en/privacy/policy#optout](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/policy#optout).

We use persistent cookies and related technologies (such as web beacons described below) to determine and track direct and indirect candidate application traffic in response to Job Postings either on  JobsAhead or on the websites of third parties through Monster’s Career-Ad-Network (described below). We also allow persistent third party cookies as part of online advertising campaigns to determine and track site traffic landing from  JobsAhead’s advertising banners that have been placed on the websites of third parties. The data collected via these cookies is anonymous and the information is not linked to your personally identifiable information without your permission. The “persistent” cookies placed by our third party ad servers will remain on your computer after you have left our site for up to 20 years unless you choose to delete them.

We also use “persistent” cookies in connection with our Career Ad Network (“CAN”). The CAN cookie is used to display relevant job ads to you on  JobsAhead and when you visit other web sites. The information collected by the CAN cookie is treated in accordance with the policies and practices described in our Privacy Statement above. The “persistent” cookie we use in CAN will remain on your computer after you have left our site and will expire six months after it was set.

You have the ability to update or opt-out of the CAN cookie by clicking on the following link: <http://can.monster.com/cookie-technology.aspx>. Monster enforces your opt-out of CAN by setting a “blocking cookie”. In order for the blocking cookie to work on your computer, your browser must be set to accept third party cookies. The blocking cookie for CAN will last for five years; however, if you delete your browser cookies, your opt-out cookie, as well as any updates you may have made, will also be deleted. In addition, your opt-out only applies in the browser you are using at the time you opt-out and only on the computer you are using at such time. If you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete this cookie, you will need to perform the opt-out task again. Opting-out of the CAN cookie does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising from CAN. It does mean that the ads delivered to you by CAN will no longer be tailored to your Web browsing patterns. Once you opt-out CAN no longer maintains a targeting cookie on your computer, so the ads will be general in nature and could be repetitive.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies at any time by modifying your browser settings. See below for instructions. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the web site.

Additionally, JobsAhead uses “Flash cookies”, also known as “Local Shared Objects”, to preserve video player settings and for user authentication purposes. You can adjust your settings for your Flash cookies [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.html).

**_Web Beacons_ :** JobsAhead Web pages and the Web pages of our partners also utilize electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs, clear gifs or action tags) that allow us to collect certain information about users’ visits to these Web pages (including the number of users who have visited those pages), measure and improve the effectiveness of advertisements and job postings, and deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique used to compile aggregated statistics about web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of page view and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. This information may be shared with third party processors for processing on behalf of JobsAhead, as well as with clients, partners, and other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Web pages, how those visitors use those Web Pages, and the effectiveness of their advertisements and job postings. (You will find information about a current third-party processor used by JobsAhead at [www.atlassolutions.com](http://www.atlassolutions.com/privacy). We may use other third party processors as well.)

Because Web beacons are the same as any other content request included in the recipe page, you cannot opt out or refuse them. However, they can be rendered ineffective by either opting out of cookies or changing the cookie setup in your browser.

**_JavaScript:_** JobsAhead also uses JavaScript, for example, within certain advertisements. JavaScript is a script language that enhances the functionality of websites, particularly in respect to pictures. We are not collecting any personal data via JavaScript but use it to inform employers about how many applicants have clicked on email addresses embedded in their job ads, for example. You may deactivate JavaScript via your browser settings or activate it the same way. If you disable JavaScript you will not be able to use some of the functions of the website.

Thank you for using JobsAhead.  
Update effective : December, 2011
